原创翻译  双语字幕
《星球日报》: 超女无处不在!
超人外出  明日之女任务加倍
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
翻译     DustD  洗七里  DerbyNinja
翻译     阿p  左左  C·A
校对     肉松  饿得慌
时间轴    想念Gallifrey的Wholock  三水
谢谢你  超女
Thank you, Supergirl.
别客气
You're welcome.
后期     你是不是饿得慌
马德里
总监     你是不是饿得慌
-谢谢你  超女  -不客气
- Gracias, Supergirl. - De nada.
卡兹尼亚南部边境
有请马斯丁总统
Please welcome President Marsdin.
早上好  我乐意回答任何问题
Good morning. I'm happy to take any questions.
抱歉我迟到了  但我给你带了礼物
I'm sorry I'm late, but I come bearing gifts.
-你去俄罗斯了吗  -卡兹尼亚
- Were you in Russia? - Kasnia.
-总统女士  总统女士  -丹弗斯小姐
- Madam President. Madam President. - Miss Danvers.
您将于《外星人赦免法》周年纪念日
You're about to hold a summit at Camp David
在戴维营召开峰会
on the anniversary of the Alien Amnesty Act.
您能浅谈一下
Can you say a few words about
这项立法在过去三年里对您有何意义吗
what this legislation has meant to you the past three years?
当然可以  该立法的影响力宽广而深远
Of course. The impact has been far-reaching and profound.
你真是身兼数职的典范
You are really good at multitasking.
有人会称其为"超"能力
Some might call it "Super."
这是我有生以来第一次  一切尽在我掌控之中
For the first time in my life, I've got everything under control.
超 女
第四季 第一集
我们在训练  各位  想好招数再往前冲
We're training, people. Never charge without a plan.
你叫詹森  是吧
Jensen, right?
是的  丹弗斯局长
Yes, Director Danvers.
放马过来吧
Let's dance.
再来
Again.
丹弗斯局长
Director Danvers,
马斯丁总统要过来做年度视察了
President Marsdin is arriving for her yearly visit.
什么时候
When?
现在
Uh, now.
什么
What?
总统女士  真没想到您会今天造访
Wow, uh, Madam President. What a surprise.
看出来了
So it seems.
请给我几分钟时间
Yes, um, if you could just give me a minute
我先去收拾一下  再接见您
then I can, uh, get cleaned up and we can chat.
多克斯特工应该在您光临之前提醒我才对
Agent Dox was supposed to give me a warning before you arrived.
我提醒了  就在她进门之前
I believe I did. Right before she entered.
难道还不够吗
Was that not enough?
我只想说  超人去了阿尔戈市
I just wanted to say, with Superman off-world on Argo,
你们超查部和超女为保证地球安全
your team and Supergirl have been doing a tremendous job
做出了杰出的贡献
keeping this planet safe.
我还想说  我认为荣恩·荣兹
And I also wanted to say I think that J'onn J'onzz
将你任命为接班人  是非常明智的选择
made a very wise choice when he chose you as his successor.
谢谢  您的话对我是莫大的鼓励
Thank you. That... That means a lot to me.
您既然来了  我就带您参观一下
Since you're here I would love to give you a tour,
看看我对部里做出的改变
show you some of the changes that I've made.
-我很乐意  -好的
- Well, I'd like that. - Okay.
你追问了总统
The way you pushed the President
关于她对外星代表团的选择  真是干得漂亮
about her alien delegation selection was perfect.
记者的任务就是要求真相
A reporter's job is to demand transparency.
既然说到这里  我希望你能
And with that said, I'd like you to talk
对今天刚刚上任的新记者们讲几句
to the cub reporters who are starting today about that.
-好啊  -嗯
- Sure. - Yeah.
凯特·格兰特不是还向你推荐了一位记者吗
And didn't Cat Grant recommend one to you?
对  她叫尼娅·纳尔
Yes, her name is Nia Nal.
尼娅·纳尔需要像你这样一位导师
Well, Nia Nal's gonna need a mentor like you.
你太了不起了  知道吗
You're incredible, you know that?
你现在背负着巨大的压力
Everything you're going through right now,
地方检察官可能会因为你守护者的身份而起诉你
the DA possibly indicting you for being Guardian,
但你却还有心思关心新记者
and here you are, worrying about cub reporters.
因为他把对付地检的任务留给了我
That's because he leaves the worrying about the DA to me.
你回来了  在大都会过得怎么样
You're back. Oh, how was Metropolis?
我可以高兴地告诉你
Oh, well, I am very happy to report
小萨在L公司东北分公司做得很出色
that Sam is doing amazing at L-Corp Northeast.
她收购的两家公司都已经开始盈利了
She has made two acquisitions that are already turning a profit.
她还在鲁比的足球队当教练
She's coaching Ruby's soccer team.
她们利用高压打法来打4-3-3阵型
Apparently, they're playing a 4-3-3 with the Gegenpress,
鲁比担任清道夫门将
and Ruby's playing as sweeper keeper.
我完全听不懂
I have no idea what that means.
意思就是她们过上了幸福的生活
I think it means they're living happily ever after.
你们接着聊
Well, I'll leave you two alone.
我还要写关于外星人峰会的文章
There's an article about an alien summit I have to write.
-我好想你  -我也是
- I have missed you. - Me too.
詹姆斯  我很担心地检的事情
James, I'm worried about this thing with the DA.
我知道你有你的策略
Listen, I know you have your strategy,
但我跟市长办公室的朋友聊过了
but I was speaking to my friends in the Mayor's office,
他们说脱身的唯一办法就是托关系
and they said the only path out of this is to use some leverage.
他们认为地检官可以被说动
They think the DA can be swayed.
-所以我在想也许我...  -莉娜  拜托
- So I was thinking that maybe I... - Lena, please.
我不希望你为了我走后门
I don't want you pulling any strings for me.
你为了跟你们家的犯罪分子划清界限
You've tried really hard to separate yourself
付出了巨大的努力
from the criminal element in your family.
别掺和这件事了
Don't get mixed up in this.
我们会处理好地检的事情
We'll handle the DA.
你愿意为我抗争  我很开心
Look, I love the fact that you want to fight for me.
真的
I do.
但我现在最需要的是
But the only thing that I need right now
你陪在我身边
is you by my side.
我叫凯斯·凯伊  我是水瓶星人
Hi. My name's Kesse Kay and I'm Aquarian.
凯斯·凯伊  欢迎你
Hi, Kesse Kay. Welcome.
我是菲奥纳
I'm Fiona.
你今天为何来参加互助会
What brings you to our group today?
因为我今天很开心
I guess I'm just happy today
想与大家分享一下
and I wanted to share it.
这是我来到地球后头一次
For the first time since I've been on this planet,
感觉自己融入了环境
I feel like I fit in.
多亏了这个
And it's 'cause of this.
形象诱发器
An image inducer.
最近不止你一个人购买了这种设备
You're not the only one who's purchased one recently.
我是上周买的
Bought it last week,
我申请了一份工作  还被录用了
applied for a job and I actually got it.
就因为我终于拥有了正常的样貌
All 'cause I look normal for once.
谁有权决定什么才是正常
Who decides what's normal?
我们为何非要佩戴这些改变外貌的设备
Why should we have to wear these devices that change our appearance
好被他人接受呢
so that we can be tolerated?
我长着獠牙
I have these tusks.
我为何要把它们藏起来
Why should I hide them?
你说起来容易
Well, that's easy for you to say.
你长得不过像个托尔金的书迷
You just look like a Tolkien fan.
你没有经历过  找了六个月的工作
You haven't been job hunting for six months
结果却被面试官称作蟑螂
and then been called a roach by your interviewer.
我们所有人都遭遇过困难  小伙子
It's not easy for any of us, young man.
沃斯博士也有他自己的痛苦
Dr. Vose has had his own struggles.
但他在核物理学方面的研究广受赞誉
But his research in nuclear physics is widely admired.
他利用自己的平台  极力提倡改变
And he's used his platform to become a great advocate for change.
我们都必须拥有被看到的勇气
We all must have the courage to be seen.
我们都在以自己的方式做出努力
We each do the best we can in our own way.
各位下周见
See you all next week.
禁区  闲人免进
有何贵干
Can I help you?
今天过得不顺哈
Rough day, huh?
拜托不要
Please don't!
我要是说我也不想这么做  你会相信吗
Would you believe me if I told you this is no fun for me either?
其实我还挺享受的
Well, maybe a little bit of fun.
我们可不希望你左右不对称
Wouldn't want you all lopsided now, would we?
你真是幼稚
You are such a child.
遇险信标
警报激活
允许访问
Access granted.
他好像不想让你们进去
I don't think he wants you going in there.
关于总统驾到这种事情
I didn't think you needed more of a heads-up
我以为你不需要提前通知
that the President was arriving.
你动作很快
You're good on your feet.
是的  我能在几微秒内处理上兆兆字节
True, I process terabytes in microseconds,
但你的速度也不慢
but you're not so slow yourself.
你处理信息的速度并没有想象中那么快
You don't process as fast as you think you do.
因为我几个月来一直在跟你强调
Because I've been telling you for months
遇到重要事件
to warn me in advance
一定要提前通知我
when things are important.
比如超女刚刚在沃斯实验室前砸了个大坑
Like Supergirl just cratered at Vose Laboratory?
-我来召集突击队  -来不及了
- I'll assemble a strike team. - There's no time.
军团万岁
Long live the legion!
不  布莱尼
No... Brainy!
-我觉得你需要后援  -布莱尼
- I thought you could use some backup. - Brainy.
是我  你现在自由了  超女
It is I. You're free now, Supergirl.
-自由  这副脚铐...  -打开了
- Free? The cuffs are still... - Opened?
我在同时执行多项任务
I was multitasking.
不客气
You're welcome.
我拿到了
Got it.
不
No!
沃斯博士
Dr. Vose.
我一听说就赶来了  你还好吗
I came as soon as I heard. Are you all right?
他们把我的獠牙给割掉了  荣恩
They cut off my tusks, J'onn.
也许我想错了  我们所有人都身处险境
Maybe I was wrong. None of us are safe.
荣恩  你怎么来了
J'onn, what are you doing here?
沃斯博士是我的朋友
Dr. Vose is a friend of mine.
我收看了袭击的新闻
I heard the attack on the news.
他是外星人权利的公开倡导者
He's an outspoken advocate for alien rights,
大概也成了仇恨犯罪的目标
and most likely the target of a hate crime.
这不是一起仇恨犯罪  荣恩
This wasn't a hate crime, J'onn.
这是一起高级别抢劫
This was a high-level robbery.
罪犯是专业人士
These criminals were professionals.
他们带了重力脚铐
They brought gravity cuffs,
从沃斯博士的实验室里抢走了电脉冲炸弹
they stole an EMP from Dr. Vose's lab.
如果他们把它引爆  可能会摧毁整个电力网
If they blow that thing, it could take out the entire power grid.
他们把他的獠牙给割掉了  超女
They cut off his tusks, Supergirl.
那是他身为外星人唯一的特征
The very thing that distinguishes him as an alien.
是的  用来骗过生物识别扫描
Yeah, to trick a biometric scan.
我最近融入了民众的生活
Look, I've been living amongst the people,
了解他们的整体状况
getting a feel for what's been going on.
现在重新涌起了一股反外星人的情绪
There's a fresh wave of anti-alien sentiment.
我能感受到
I can feel it.
我对你朋友的遭遇深表同情
Look, I'm really sorry about what happened to your friend,
但我认为  在本案中
but I think, in this case,
他身为外星人只是个偶然
the fact that he's an alien is just happenstance.
我去凯特科上班要迟到了  布莱尼在负责此案
I'm late for CatCo, but Brainy's on the case
我们会找到他们的  我保证
and we will find them, I promise.
好吧
All right.
我回来了  刚才去帮了超女的忙
I'm back, having assisted Supergirl,
非常值得
which was highly rewarding.
你能帮上忙  我很开心
I'm very happy you were able to help.
但我们之间貌似存在沟通问题
But we seem to be having a communication problem.
不  我向你保证  我能听懂
Oh, no, I assure you I understand every word
你所说的每一句话
that comes out of your mouth.
是
Yes.
但是你却理解不了
But you are not comprehending it.
不然在过去的三个月里
Otherwise, you wouldn't have spent the last three months
你就不会一直碍我的事
acting like a grain of sand in my boot.
这听起来确实很烦人
I guess that does sound annoying.
是的  我每次分配给你一项任务
Yes. Every time I tell you to do something,
你要么做得不到位  要么做得太过火
you either do too little or too much.
-是的  但是我觉得...  -这里不是军团
- Yes, but I felt-- - This isn't the Legion.
你不能随心所欲  胡作非为
Okay, you don't get to just go rogue whenever you feel like it.
所以从现在起  除非经我同意
So from now on, you don't leave this building,
否则你不得离开大楼半步
you don't breathe
甚至不准呼吸
unless I tell you to.
明白了吗
Is that understood?
-明白  -很好
- Affirmative. - Good.
我现在能呼吸了吗
May I breathe now?
不好意思  先别关门
Excuse me, sorry. Hold the elevator!
Excuse me. Hold the elevator!
-好的  -谢谢
- I got it. - Thank you.
谢谢
Thank you.
我严重迟到了
Oh, I am so late.
关键是我平时一贯准时  从不迟到
You know, the crazy thing is I am always punctual. Always.
但就在最重要的这一天
But the one day it matters,
我的新室友错拿了我租车的钥匙
my new roommate took the keys to my rental car.
当然是不小心的
Accidentally, of course.
然后我不得不搭公车
And then I had to take the bus,
结果洒了满裙子的咖啡
and I spilled coffee all over my skirt.
我只是想
And all I wanted to do
留个好的第一印象给...
was make a good first impression on Miss...
丹弗斯小姐  是你
Danvers. It's you.
是卡拉  我认识你吗
Uh, it's Kara. And do I know you?
卡拉·丹弗斯
Um... Kara Danvers.
卡拉·丹弗斯...
Kara Danvers. Wow. Um...
-我是尼娅·纳尔  -尼娅
- I'm Nia Nal. - Oh, Nia.
尼娅  很高兴认识你
Nia, it's so nice to meet you.
凯特说了很多你的好话
Cat says amazing things about you.
-真的吗  -是啊
- Really? - Yeah.
-对了  你的咖啡  -谢谢
- Oh, the coffee's for you. - Oh, thanks.
-真抱歉  -谢谢
- I'm sorry. - Thank you.
你是名记者  你不需要给我买咖啡
You're a reporter. You don't have to get me coffee.
我知道  但是格兰特女士说你喜欢拿铁
Oh, I know, um, but Miss Grant mentioned you like lattes
所以我就想着带一杯
so I thought I'd pick one up.
她说你喜欢保持一定温度的咖啡
She said you were particular about the temperature,
所以我把一切都计算好了
so I had it all perfectly planned out,
但是我的计划全乱了  都赖我那室友
but then my plan went haywire, no thanks to my roommate,
然后我...
and I, uh...
这可能已经太凉了  对不起
It's probably too cold by now. I'm sorry.
天啊
Oh, my God.
你跟我一模一样
You're me.
-有吗  -是啊  相当的...
- I am? - Yeah, totally. It's...
简直像死了
It's unnerving.
我怎么像你了
How am I you?
我是在模仿你吗  我完全可以停下来
Am I... Am I being you now? I can totally stop whatever it is.
我只是想做好工作
I just wanna be good at my job.
没  没事的  别太上心  咱们...
Hey, no, it's okay. Don't worry about it. Let's just...
咱们去开会吧
Let's get into the meeting.
你好
Hello.
地检办公室又有新消息了
Got another update from the DA's office.
或许你想知道  奥尔森的情况越来越糟了
Things are looking worse for Olsen. Thought you'd want to know.
谢谢
Thank you.
那东西要是砸到我硬盘
That thing hits my hard drives,
1996年全家度假的情景可要重现了
it'll be family vacation 1996 all over again.
只不过这次
Only this time,
没有医疗人员会来救你了
the paramedics won't be there to resuscitate you.
真扫兴
Buzzkill.
我看到好医生很友善
I see the good doctor was amiable.
劝沃斯费了不少功夫
Vose took some convincing,
但是的
but yes.
然后超女出现了
And then Supergirl showed up.
电磁脉冲呢
And the EMP?
渴望和平的人要做好打仗的准备
Let him who desires peace prepare for war.
丹佛斯小姐  卡拉
Miss Danvers... Kara.
你想见我
You wanted to see me?
是  我只是想确认下
Yeah, I was just checking in.
我知道詹姆斯让新记者
I know James asked the new reporters
列一个新闻点的清单
to pitch in a list of story ideas.
-你选好文章了吗  -是的
- Did you pick an article? - Yes.
纳欣诺市新时尚区的未来
Uh, the feature on National City's new fashion district.
真的吗
Really?
你觉得这个不好吗
You don't think it's a good idea?
挺好的  只是我看到你简历上写着
It's fine. It's just I read on your resume
你有乔治城的
that you have a degree
国际关系学学位
in International Relations from Georgetown.
你确定你不想做一些
Are you sure you don't want to do
比较更有影响的文章吗
something with a little more heft?
时尚也很有影响  卡拉
But there's nothing slight about fashion, Kara.
那是一种最本能的艺术形式
It's one of the most visceral forms of art.
我们的穿着决定了我们是谁
What we choose to wear tells a story about who we are.
不管你是选择黑色皮革还是粉彩丝绸
Whether you wear black and leather or pastels and silk,
你都是在创造一个内心中的自我
you're creating an inner version of yourself
不管你有没有意识到
whether you realize it or not.
我还从来没这么想过衣着呢
Never really thought about clothes that way.
这个故事最出彩的点在于
Well, what makes this story so exciting
时尚区正准备在
is that the fashion district's setting up shop
东城中心开商店
in the middle of East City.
新的法规可以让设计者们的生活与工作
New legislation is allowing designers to live
都在一个空间里进行
and to work in industrial spaces
这中模式已经被抛弃好几十年了
that have been abandoned for decades.
一个孕育犯罪的地区
An area that's been a hotbed for crime
将会输入丰富的色彩与生命
is going to be infused with color and life.
想象下生长在这种环境下的孩子们
I just think of all the kids growing up in that neighborhood,
那些由此新产生的工作机会
all the new job opportunities that'll be created.
我想写的时尚区的文章
The fashion district article I wanna write about
不是关于衣服的
isn't about clothes,
是关于社区与发展
it's about community and growth.
还有希望
And hope.
你得这样去向詹姆斯推这篇文章
You need to pitch the article exactly like that to James.
他肯定会喜欢
He's gonna love it.
-真的吗  -当然
- Really? - Yeah.
真是太感谢你了
Well, thank you very much.
-布莱尼  怎么了  -绝对不是我
- Brainy, what's up? - Definitely not me.
我被丹弗斯主管禁足了
I was grounded by Director Danvers.
但当我被锁在办公桌上时  不是真的上了锁
But while I was chained to my desk, not literally,
我拼接了沃斯实验室各种监控的图像
I stitched together various images from surveillance
然后进行了匹配
at Vose's lab and ran them.
图像残缺不全
The images were rudimentary
并且找到了754231个嫌犯
and brought up 754,231 potential suspects.
我将所有图像与已知关联人物进行了交叉检验
I cross-checked each image with known associates
将验证范围降到了两个人上
and narrowed identification down to two.
奥蒂斯与默茜·格雷夫斯
Otis and Mercy Graves.
姐弟小组
A brother and sister team.
-你有地址吗  -没有
- Do you have a location? - Negative.
但是  我找到了一名前员工
Hower, I was able to identify an ex-employer
或许能帮助你定位到地址
who might be able to help you with an address.
是谁
Who's that?
卢瑟小姐  你有来访者
Miss Luthor, you have a visitor.
莉娜
Lena.
我的天
Oh, dear.
我希望你今天下午来找我时
I hope I didn't have that same expression
我脸上不是那副表情
when you showed up this afternoon.
不  母亲  你一如既往
No, Mother, your face was
戴着猜不透的面具
a mask of enigma as usual.
所以我才显得年轻
It's what keeps me looking young.
你怎么来这了
What are you doing here?
真有趣  我也可以问你一样的问题
Funny, I could ask you the same question.
我得找到默茜和奥蒂斯·格雷夫斯
I need to find Mercy and Otis Graves.
他们曾为莱克斯工作
They worked for Lex.
后来又在卡德摩斯为你工作
And then for you. Cadmus.
默茜以前是莱克斯的安全主管
Mercy was Lex's head of security.
后来做了污点证人  背叛了他
And then turned State's evidence on him, betrayed him.
让他进了监狱
Put him behind bars.
所以你认为我会出于复仇心而帮助你
So you think I'd help you as some sort of revenge?
我不再抱有复仇心了
I'm not vengeful anymore.
在这里我的心变大了好几倍
My heart's grown several sizes in here.
让人没法过圣诞节的人还好意思说
Says the Grinch who stole Christmas.
几个月前
A few months ago
当地球遭到另外那些氪星人的环境改造时
when the planet was being terraformed by those other Kryptonians,
我在牢房里  躲在床垫下
I was in my cell, under a mattress,
希望天花板不要塌下来砸死我
hoping the ceiling wouldn't fall and crush me.
然后我意识到  我不想孤零零地死去
And I realized I didn't want to die alone.
假如我不想孤零零地死去
And if I didn't want to die alone,
我必须做出改变
I had to change.
所以  除了格雷夫斯姐弟是对怪物
So, what do you want to know about the Grave siblings,
你还想知道他们什么事
besides they're monsters?
把卡德摩斯的据点列给我
A list of every Cadmus location
他们可能用来藏身的据点
you think they might be using to hide.
只要国内的  还是包括国外的
Just domestic? Or international?
我记错时间了吗
Did I get the time wrong?
不  其他人都没来
No. No one else showed up.
在沃斯博士遇袭后  他们很害怕
After Dr. Vose was attacked, they're scared.
-你来自伊克萨诺星  对吗  -是的
- You're from Ichthanor, am I right? - I am.
也就是说你有共情能力
Which means you're an empath.
尽管有时我希望我没有
Although, sometimes I wish I weren't.
正是这样的事让我离开伊克萨诺星
Things like this are why I left Ichthanor.
说起来  英国也一样
And England, for that matter.
我不能再逃避了
I can't run anymore.
我一直在和大家交流
I've been talking to people,
调查威胁过我们的人类
researching humans who've threatened us.
我们邻里间组织了一个巡逻小组来反抗
We're starting a patrol group in the neighborhood to fight back.
你想加入我们吗
Would you join us?
我曾在前线奋战多年
I've been fighting on the front line for a long time now.
我已经退休了
Those days are behind me.
我发过誓要过平静的生活
I made a vow to live a peaceful life,
以另一种方式支持人们
stand up for people in a different way.
去死吧  害虫们
Die, roaches!
趴下
Get down!
超女
Supergirl.
这是仇恨犯罪  毫无疑问
This was a hate crime, no doubt about it.
我同意
Agreed.
我仍旧认为对沃斯博士的袭击
I still believe the attack on Dr.Vose
是出于反外星人的情绪
was motivated by anti-alien sentiment.
他是这个互助小组的一员
He was a member of a support group here.
你该调查一下两起袭击有没有关联
You should dig into it, see if the two attacks were connected.
可袭击沃斯博士的是前卡德摩斯人员
But Dr. Vose's lab was robbed by ex-Cadmus operatives.
这是酒吧外的爆炸
This... This was an explosion outside of a bar.
我不觉得它们有所关联
I don't think there's any reason to believe they're related.
我不会排除那个可能性
I wouldn't dismiss the possibility.
我一直想让你明白
I've been trying to tell you
大众对外星人的态度正在改变
the climate towards aliens is changing.
是的  我同意  但是是变得更好了
Yeah. Yes, I agree it is, but for the better.
的确  永远会有极端主义者
And yes, there will always be extremists
比如这些袭击酒吧的人
like whoever attacked the bar,
可总的而言  我认为这个国家进步极大
but overall, I think this country has made incredible progress.
总统即将庆祝
The President is about to celebrate
《外星人赦免法》两周年
the second anniversary of the Alien Amnesty Act.
这是地球上第一次
For the first time on Earth,
外星人被当做有平等权利的公民
aliens are embraced as citizens with equal rights --
这也是引发强烈抵制的原因
Which is part of the backlash.
外星人的同化激发了许多人类的恐惧
The assimilation with aliens has sparked fear among many humans.
外星人感受到了那份愤怒的冲击
And aliens are feeling the brunt of that anger.
我就是外星人  我最近飞遍世界各地
I'm an alien, and I've been all over the world recently
我从未感受到如此多的爱意
and I have never felt more love.
人们拥戴你为英雄的部分原因
Part of the reason why you were embraced as a hero
是因为你看起来像个人类
is because you present as a human.
大部分外星人没有这种特权
Most aliens do not share that privilege.
恐怕你的经验不能作为最佳衡量标准
I'm afraid your experiences are not the best barometer here.
人们拥戴我为英雄是因为我尽职
I'm embraced as a hero because I'm good at my job.
并且我真的很不喜欢你质疑我的判断
And I really don't appreciate you questioning my judgment.
我只是想为你提供另一个视角
I'm just trying to offer you a different perspective.
荣恩  你已经离开超查部了
J'onn, you left the DEO.
或许你现在该把保护城市的任务交给我
So maybe now it's time you leave protecting the city to me.
看来发生口角了
That looked contentious.
她总是那么顽固吗
Is she always that stubborn?
她想保持希望
She wants to remain hopeful.
那也是我最钦佩她的事情之一
It's one of the things I most admire about her.
你把炒饭都吃光了吗
Did you finish the fried rice?
抱歉  我这是压力性暴食
I'm sorry. I'm stress-eating.
约会不顺利吗
Did you have a bad date?
不  约会其实
No, the dating, it's actually...
-非常顺利  -真的吗
- It's been great. - Really?
不  不要满脸那个表情
No, don't get that look on your face
好像你要主持我的婚礼一样
like you're gonna officiate my wedding.
不  我还没有遇到想长期交往的女人
No, I have not met a woman that I'm that serious about yet,
所以...
so, you know...
不过  重新开始约会感觉很好
But it's...it's good to get out there.
那很好啊
Well, that's great.
那你为什么狂吃捞面
So, why are you scarfing the lo mein?
因为布莱尼  天呐
Brainy. Oh, my God.
抱歉  但是每一件事
I'm sorry, but everything...
他做的每一件事都惹我上火
Everything he does just infuriates me.
我知道这样很过分  但是...
I know it's mean, but it's just...
我控制不了
I can't help it.
他对这个时代还不熟悉
He's new to this time period.
需要努力适应
It's a big adjustment.
我相信肯定不容易  尽量对他宽容一点
I'm sure it's been hard. Try to go easy on him.
我会尽量
I'll try.
那你呢
What about you?
我吗  我们叫了你最喜欢的中餐外卖
Me? We ordered your favorite Chinese takeout
你却一点都没吃
and you haven't even taken a bite.
怎么了
What's going on?
世界不是尽在你掌控中吗
I thought you were on top of the world.
我和荣恩吵了一架
I got in a fight with J'onn.
-在发生酒吧袭击事件之后  -真的吗
- After the attack, at the bar. - Really?
他想说服我  目前存在
He tried to convince me that there's this
针对外星人的仇恨运动
hate movement against aliens.
是我疯了吗
I mean, am I crazy?
我觉得这个世界比以往任何时候都美好
I feel like the world is better than it's ever been.
更多元化  认同度更高
More diversity, more acceptance.
当然  从某些程度上来说
Sure. I mean, in some ways.
自从荣恩离开超查部后
Ever since J'onn left the DEO,
我感觉跟他那么疏远
I just feel so far from him.
我不知道他过着怎样的生活
I don't really know what his life is like.
-嗯  -我只知道我不喜欢他的新观点
- Yeah. - All I know is I hate his new point of view.
有种不祥的感觉
It feels so ominous.
荣恩并不是在危言耸听  卡拉
J'onn is not an alarmist, Kara.
如果他要告诉你些什么  换做是我会听的
I mean, if he's trying to tell you something, I would listen.
你在害怕些什么
What are you so afraid of?
我什么也不怕
I'm not afraid of anything. It...
我终于感觉世界是如此美好
I just finally feel like the world is good.
我很希望能保持下去
And I so badly want it to stay that way,
即使只是一小会
even if it's just for a little while.
卡拉·丹弗斯
Kara Danvers,
你是我认识的最勇敢的人
you are the most courageous person I know.
就算是艰难的状况  只要你肯面对
And even if it's hard, if you face it,
就能克服一切
you can conquer anything.
我试试吧
I'll try.
只要你能克服不对布莱尼动手的冲动
Only if you conquer the urge to not punch Brainy in the face.
这个交易太不公平了
That is an unfair bargain.
将死
Checkmate.
你就是喜欢对我说这句话是吧
You just love saying that to me, don't you?
不  我也平息了自己的怒火  母亲
No, I've let go of my anger, too, Mother.
-我不能把力气浪费在仇恨上  -对
- I can't waste my energy on it. - Right.
你需要集中你所有的精力来拯救世界
You need all your energy to focus on saving the world.
虽然我看到的
Although, all I've seen
只有你那款形象诱发器的广告
are the commercials of your image inducer.
众目睽睽之下完美地隐藏外星人
Making a mint hiding aliens in plain sight.
那与政治无关  母亲  只是生意而已
It's not political, Mother, it's just business.
它能为我其他的重要研究提供资金支持
It helps fund my other research, the important kind.
你从来都是个实用主义者
Ever the pragmatist.
你这次来有何目的
And this visit?
我知道跟我下象棋是一种乐趣
I know chess with me is a good time,
但你短短几天内来探视了我两次
but the love of the game can't be the only reason
不可能只是因为喜欢下象棋
I've seen you twice in as many days.
想听实话吗
The truth?
是因为詹姆斯有可能遭到起诉
It's James and the looming indictment.
这让我开始思考我的人生
It made me think about my life,
我有很长一段时间都自我封闭
how much of it I've spent living on an island.
我想回归社会  重新建立我所丢失的关系
I wanna reconnect, rebuild the relationships that I've lost.
没错  这其中也包括你
And yes, that does include you.
无论如何  你都是我的母亲
For better or for worse, you're still my mother.
虽然生活并不总是如意
Things weren't always rosy,
但我们也曾共度过美好时光
but there were some good times.
甚至是与莱克斯
Even with Lex.
你们俩反目成仇  令我很难过
It made me sad when the two of you became enemies.
如果我还有报复心的话
If I was still vengeful,
我会怪超人
I'd blame Superman
拆散了我们的家庭
for tearing this family apart.
好吧  我确实还有报复心
Okay, I'm still vengeful.
我倒不觉得这全是超人的错
I don't know if it was all Superman.
在我看来  是他与布鲁诺·曼海姆的关系
In my opinion, it was his relationship with Bruno Mannheim
使他走上了错误的不归路
that started him down the wrong path.
那个恶棍
That miscreant?
他们曾是生意伙伴  没错
They were business partners, sure,
但布鲁诺当初只是为了洗钱
but Bruno was only in it for the money laundering.
他利用了你哥哥的生意  然后又抛弃了他
It's a shame how he used your brother's business
实在可耻
and then dumped him.
我都不知道布鲁诺还利用卢瑟公司洗过钱
I didn't know Bruno laundered money through Luthor Corp.
我的账簿上有什么需要我担心的账目吗
Is there anything in my books I need to worry about,
毕竟你是那个知道所有犯罪细节的人
since you know where all the bodies are buried?
看来我该教教你了
I guess it's time I educated you.
好的  萨姆  从这个角度写流浪汉危机很犀利
All right. Sam, it's a smart angle on the homeless crisis.
交给你了
It's all yours.
有人想尝试时尚板块吗
All right, anybody else want to take a crack at fashion?
我建议将纳欣诺市
My pitch is to emphasize
定义为全球时尚中心
that National City as a global epicenter of fashion.
我们掀起热点  引领潮流
We dictate what's hot, we set the trends.
我们早就该打造一片夺目的时尚新区
And we're far overdue for a glossy new fashion district
代表我们的文化价值了
to represent our cultural importance.
而且  我母亲跟艾德里安·泰勒是大学同学
FYI, my mother went to college with Adrian Tyler,
他可是美国目前最著名的设计师
the most famous living American designer, so,
所以我几乎可以采访到时尚界的任何人
I have access to almost anyone in this field for interviews.
公开采访哦
On the record.
很好  还有谁想尝试时尚板块吗
Nice. Okay, anybody else want to take a crack at fashion?
我再问最后两次  最后一次
Going once, going twice.
麦肯齐  交给你了
MacKenzie, all yours.
布莱尼
Brainy.
我利用你从莉莉安·卢瑟那里得到的信息
I used the info you got from Lillian Luthor
找到了默茜和奥蒂斯的下落
and found a location for Mercy and Otis.
你能相信会是在一间废弃仓库吗
Would you believe it's an abandoned warehouse?
这里没有人
There's no one here.
我三十分钟前还能检测到热信号
I had heat signatures there 30 minutes ago.
我这就黑进电脑系统
I'm hacking into the computer network.
扫描一下潜在线索
We'll scan for potential leads.
稍等一下
Hold on, please.
"我在我儿子学校查到了一个佛里人"
"有人知道怎么除掉他吗"
"I have a lead on a Phorian at my son's school."
厉害  我这就发你个链接  教你怎么制造炸弹
怎么制造炸弹
How to make a bomb?
杀死外星人  地球第一
地球第一
Earth first?
接听电话
正在通话
你终于接电话了
Hey, I'm glad you picked up.
你卖给我的武器  根本伤不到佛里人
That weapon you sold me, it barely burned through the Phorians.
-你是谁  -什么意思  我是凯伦
- Who is this? - What do you mean? It's Karen.
妈  凯瑞不让我用电脑
Mom, Cary won't let me use the computer.
我先挂了
I've got to go.
外星人抢我工作
如何杀死佛里人
总觉得有外星人躲在我家附近
杀掉那些蟑螂
刚砸了外星人的车 感觉很爽
布莱尼
Brainy,
这些电脑上的聊天室
these chat rooms on these computers...
都是从暗网过滤来的
All filtered through the dark web.
服务器网址遍布全国
ISPs originated from all over the country.
却无法追踪
Yet untraceable.
但我在一封删掉的邮件缓存中查到了线索
But I did find something in a deleted e-mail cache.
戴维营的设计图纸
Blueprints of Camp David.
默茜和奥蒂斯
Mercy and Otis.
他们要袭击总统的外星人峰会
They're going to attack the President's alien summit.
你之前说得对
You were right about the crimes.
那些犯罪都是仇恨引起的
They were motivated by hate,
而且他们有一群人...
and there's a web of people--
既然你知道了真相  就可以抗争了  卡拉
Now that you know what's happening, you can fight it, Kara.
但我需要你的帮助
But I need your help.
他们要袭击外星人峰会
They're going to attack the alien summit.
帮我保护现场
Help me keep it safe.
再帮我阻止这个组织的其他行动
And then help me take on the rest of this movement
这个组织比我见过的任何敌人都壮大
because it is bigger than anything I have ever fought.
参与其中的人
The people involved in it
就像是我每天在拯救的人
are like the people I save every day.
我知道如何阻止恶徒  但这些人...
A villain, I know how to stop, but these people...
抱歉  但我不能和你并肩作战
I'm sorry, but I cannot fight with you.
这次不行
Not this time.
但你必须这样做
But... But you have to.
是你第一个发现的  是你...
You were the first person to see this. You...
让我睁开双眼看清这一切
Who yelled at me to open my eyes!
你怎么能不参与进来呢
How can you not join me now?
因为这不再是我的战役
Because it's no longer my path to fight.
我父亲过世时  给我留下了一句话
When my father passed, he gave me a message.
"如赫隆米尔教导的那样  促进和平"
"Live as H'ronmeer taught and promote peace."
我不能拿着剑来促进和平
I cannot do that whilst holding a sword.
我会帮助需要帮助的人
I will help those in need,
我也会像沃斯医生一样提倡改变
and I will be a voice for change like Dr. Vose.
我会支持你  卡拉
I will support you, Kara.
但我不能陪你去战斗
But I cannot join your battle.
很抱歉
I'm sorry.
对不起  超女  我做不到
I'm sorry, Supergirl, but I can't.
我不会取消峰会
I won't cancel the summit.
格雷夫斯姐弟非常危险
The Graves siblings are dangerous operatives.
我很担心他们会伤害你和外星宾客
I'm afraid of what they could do to you and your alien guests.
我也担心
So am I.
但总会有令人担心的事
But there's always someone to be afraid of.
某种不受我们控制的力量或威胁
Some force, some threat that is beyond our control.
但我们必须继续前行
And yet, we carry on.
向恐惧妥协的人算不上领袖
A leader who caves to fear is no leader at all.
我会通知特勤处  超查部
I'll alert the Secret Service, the DEO,
我们会一起合作
we'll co-ordinate with them.
戴维营
-你还好吗  -没事
- You doing okay? - Yeah.
谢谢你能来
And thanks for being here.
我知道你现在不是每场战役都出席
I know you pick your battles now.
这次战役很有吸引力
Well, it seemed like a good battle to pick.
你们能来真是太好了
I'm thrilled that you're here.
要知道这是戴维营历史上
You know this is the first time in history
第一次接待非本星球的宾客
that we've hosted guests that were not born on this planet.
至少已知情况是这样
At least that we, uh, know about.
艾森豪威尔总统
President Eisenhower named
给戴维营起名时用了
it Camp David after his son and grandson,
儿子和孙子的名字  都是戴维
who were both named, of course, David.
艾丽克斯  是电脉冲炸弹
Alex. It's the EMP.
求救  求救  直升机正在坠落
Mayday, mayday! Chopper is going down.
大家保持冷静  都别乱动
Hey, everybody, stay calm. Nobody move.
不要乱动
Nobody move.
查看周围情况
Secure the perimeter.
那是电脉冲炸弹
That was the EMP.
快  多克斯特工
Now, Agent Dox.
反波长装置已启动
Wavelength countermeasures active.
成功了  干得漂亮  布莱尼
It worked! Nice one, Brainy.
太好了
Eureka!
这里的灯都炸了
The lights are blown in here.
我们得把总统转移到安全屋
We gotta move the President to the safe room.
刚才只是调虎离山
That was just a distraction.
总统女士
Madam President.
你觉得他们就在附近吗
Do you think they're inside the perimeter?
肯定在
I know they are.
好了  带她进去
All right, take her back.
你们去确保房间安全
You guys, go, clear the house.
艾丽克斯  他们穿着超查部制服
Alex, they're in DEO uniforms.
大家都没事吗
Okay, is everybody okay back there?
没事  把她带出去
We're good, let's get her out.
快走  快
Now, go, now.
你会没事的  女士
You'll be fine, ma'am.
-你还好吗  -我没事
- Are you all right? - I'm fine!
抓住他们
Just get them.
超女  我知道你听得见
Supergirl! I know you can hear me.
不打死的小强
You filthy roach.
告诉你  这是你阻止不了的
You need to know you won't stop this.
我要阻止你们两个
I'm stopping you both.
这不是你以往的那种正义与邪恶的斗争
This isn't one of your battles where it's good versus evil.
因为这次我们是正义的
Because we are the good guys,
我们为了拯救这个国家而战斗
fighting to save this country.
我们会不惜一切取得胜利
We'll do whatever it takes to win.
救命
Help!
超女
Supergirl!
你真以为
You really thought
我姐姐会杀了我吗
my sister would kill me?
你以为今晚你阻止了我们
You think you stopped us tonight,
但导火索已经引燃
but the fuse was lit.
那景象将是美妙绝伦
And it's gonna be beautiful.
大家都安全了  总统没事  你抓住他了吗
Everyone's safe here. The President's fine. Did you get him?
只抓住一个
Only one.
你可以嘴硬反抗
You can act as tough as you want,
但我们会让你说出默茜的下落
but you are gonna tell us where Mercy went.
到那时  你就会后悔自己没有早点说出来
And when you do, you're gonna wish you had done it sooner.
把他带走
Just take him.
老天  我真讨厌那家伙
God, I hate that guy.
这些东西你从哪弄来的
Where did you get all that stuff?
艾克沙修的漫画书店
The comic book store on Excelsior.
那家店就在温的公寓那条街上
Oh, that's right down the street from Winn's apartment.
还有这件羊毛衫  温有件一模一样的
And that cardigan. Winn has the same one.
是吗
Does he?
好吧  没错
All right, yes.
是这样  我分析了我们最近的一系列冲突
You see, I analyzed our recent torrent of conflicts
并没有找到其中共同的原因
and I couldn't find a common factor.
我按你的方式来
I did things your way,
是错的
wrong.
我按军团的方式来  还是错的
I did things the Legion way, wrong.
我按自己的方式来
I did things my way,
就更加错了
so very wrong.
我就是做不好
I just couldn't win.
于是我就意识到  问题就在这里
And then I realized, that's it.
我做不好是因为我不是温
I can't win because I'm not Winn.
他是你的...  你的好兄弟
He was your... Your bro.
我不是他
I'm not him.
除非...
Unless...
除非我...  我能变成他
Unless I... I am.
我不是...
I'm not...
我不是很容易适应变化
I'm not very good with change.
我也确实想念温
And I do miss Winn.
很想念
A lot.
或许我在某种程度上
And I guess in some ways, I have been
因为你不是他而惩罚你
punishing you for not being him.
这样
And that is...
这不公平
That's not fair.
我明白
I understand.
我也想念我的朋友
I miss my friends, too.
抱歉  我差点忘了
I'm sorry, I didn't even think about that.
你把他们丢下了
And you left them behind.
严格地说  他们走在我们前面
Well, technically, they're ahead.
对
Right. Yes.
不管怎样  我们俩也摆脱不了彼此
Look, either way, we are stuck with each other.
所以...  这...不是坏事
So... No, I mean, that's not a bad thing.
其实是好事
It's actually a good thing.
其实  我们只用...找到我们的节奏
You know? We just have to... Find our rhythm.
这我倒能行
That, I can do.
人家都说我节奏感很好
I've been told I have excellent rhythm.
-不不  -就让我...  好吧
- No. No. - Just let me... All right.
别再穿毛衣了  行吗
Just no more sweaters, okay?
那最好了  这东西束手束脚的
Thank God. These things are restrictively tight.
这是个停车场
It was parking lots.
布鲁诺从你哥手上收购了家子公司
Bruno purchased them through
然后以子公司的名义买的
a subsidiary he bought from your brother.
我妈妈接着报出了五个
My mother goes on to name
曼海姆手下空壳公司的名字
five more shell companies owned by Mannheim.
你是地方检察官  叫他们拿出公司账簿来
You're the District Attorney. Subpoena their books.
曼海姆违反了《反诈骗腐败组织犯罪法》
You'll find enough RICO violations
你可以送他进监狱  关得跟阿尔·卡彭一样久
to send Mannheim away for as long as Al Capone.
阿尔·卡彭  美国著名黑手党芝加哥机构老板
那你妈妈知道你耍了她吗
So does your mother know you played her?
她很快就会知道
She will soon.
等...
No...
那你另一个案子呢
And your other investigation?
守护者算什么
Guardian who?
尼娅
Nia.
跟詹姆斯的那场会议你怎么回事
What happened in that meeting with James?
麦肯齐已经提出要接下那篇文章了
Well, uh, MacKenzie pitched her take on the article
她的处理方式也很好
and she had a good approach.
你的更好
Yours was better.
你跟我一个人说的时候那么有激情
You were so passionate when you talked to just me about it.
为什么当时就不说话了
Why'd you shut down?
那房间太可怕了
It was a scary room.
詹姆斯·奥尔森是这大媒体集团的总裁
James Olsen is the CEO of this incredible media empire.
麦肯齐的名人朋友比奥普拉还多
And MacKenzie has more famous friends than Oprah.
尼娅  麦肯齐接报道时
Nia, what really happened
你到底怎么回事
when MacKenzie took that article?
你为什么不想竞争
Why didn't you want to compete?
可能我那时
I guess, in the moment,
还是担心起冲突
I was afraid to make waves.
好吧  是因为恐惧
Okay. Fear.
我理解
I get that.
无论我们多相信自己  恐惧都不会消失
No matter how much we believe in ourselves, that never goes away.
不会完全消失
Not fully.
即便我现在觉得自己无所畏惧
Even now, I think I'm not afraid of anything.
但总会出现新的恶人
And then, something new and ugly rears its head,
让我又迷茫起来
and chases me right back down the rabbit hole.
但一旦我们找到自己
But once we catch ourselves,
我们必须重新回到现实
we have to jump right back out there.
所以你害怕起冲突
So, you're afraid to make waves?
好的  尽管去做
Okay. Make them anyway.
搞一个大事件
Make a tsunami.
-你是对的  -当然
- You're right. - Of course I am.
找到恐惧  然后击败它
Acknowledge the fear, then kick its ass.
-谢谢你  卡拉  -不用谢我
- Thank you, Kara. - Don't thank me.
赶紧出去  搞一个大事件
Just get out there and kick up a storm.
加油吧  真的  时间飞逝
Come on, seriously. Time's a-wasting.
抓紧时间
Ticktock.
你知道你正在转变成凯特  对吧
You realize you're turning into Cat, right?
什么  不会的
What? No.
真的  这有点吓到我
To a tee. It's kind of freaking me out.
你刚刚说了"抓紧时间"
You just said "Ticktock."
你差点就说"快去"了
You might as well have said "Chop chop."
-我刚刚说了吗  -是的  你说了
- Did I say that? - Yeah, you did.
重大新闻  所有对詹姆斯·奥尔森的指控
We have breaking news. All charges against James Olsen...
我的天
Oh, my God.
将被撤销
will be dropped.
-詹姆斯  -随着事情的进展
- James. - More as this story develops.
看见没  告诉你没什么好担心的
See? Told you there was nothing to worry about.
我太开心了  詹姆斯
I am so happy, James.
我也是
Me too.
谢谢你一直在我身边
And thank you for standing by my side
让我自己处理这件事
and letting me handle this by myself.
我从不怀疑你可以处理好
I never doubted you could handle it.
我提供帮助仅仅因为太多的家人都进了监狱
I only offered because I've lost so much of my family to prison,
这让我的生活和人际关系混乱复杂
it's turned my life and my relationships upside down
我没法想象这件事发生在你身上
and I couldn't bear the thought of that happening to you.
不会的
It won't.
是的  我们将不会对詹姆斯·奥尔森
Yes, we will not be indicting James Olsen
过去的妨碍执法提起诉讼
for past allegations of obstruction.
但是如果奥尔森先生继续扮演守护者一角
However, if Mr. Olsen were to resume his role as Guardian
詹姆斯·奥尔森将不会被起诉
他将会被直接逮捕
he will be subject to immediate arrest.
还有一个案子
On a separate investigation,
我们发现了新的证据
our office has uncovered new
在州诉布鲁诺·曼海姆的案件上
evidence in the State's case against Bruno Mannheim.
我们将重新起诉
We will be reissuing the indictment
这将会包括几项洗钱罪名
which will include several counts of money laundering.
你刚才听见的是  地方检察官迪亚兹重申
There you have it, district Attorney Diaz reiterating...
所以  关于昨天
So, about yesterday...
我知道那对你多么重要
I know how much it means to you
尊重你父亲的遗愿
to honor your father's wishes.
我不该让你违背诺言
And I shouldn't have asked you to compromise that.
我知道过去几天
Look, I know the last few days
你很艰难
have been difficult for you.
我很抱歉我让你更艰难了
I'm just sorry I made it even more so.
一想到外界充斥着愤怒
The thought of so much anger out there is...
我不想相信那是真的
It's not what I wanted to believe was true.
我以为这个国家
I thought this country...
我们处在一个更好的地方
That we were in a better place.
一想到要争取的东西有这么多
The idea of having to fight something so vast,
试着去团结
trying to unite
一个如此分裂的世界  这真的是
such a divided world, it's...
压力巨大
It's overwhelming.
你的乐观会拯救我们的  卡拉
It's your optimism that will help save us, Kara.
你是希望的明灯  为我们树立榜样
You're the beacon of hope who sets an example,
到处为正义而战
fighting for justice everywhere.
你是团结和同情的代名词
The voice of unity and compassion
这会引发改变
that will inspire change.
我感觉自己什么都不知道
I feel like I don't know anything.
那你比想象中聪明多了
Then you are wiser than you realize.
我们现在播报一则重大新闻
We now take you to a late-breaking news story.
从戴维营刺杀未遂事件
Shocking footage acquired
获得的惊人录像
from the assassination attempt at Camp David
揭示了总统是一个外星人
has revealed that the President is an alien.
这证实了许多
This confirms what many
边缘团体的狂妄猜想
thought to be the ravings of a fringe group.
专家已经鉴定了录像
Experts have authenticated the footage
并没有篡改的痕迹
and found no signs of doctoring.
美国总统是一个外星人
The President of the United States is an alien.
"导火索已经引燃"
"The fuse was lit."
阿尔  菲奥纳在这吗
Al, is Fiona here?
不  她轮班时没有出现
No, she didn't show up for her shift.
这些指控似乎是正确的
These accusations seem to be true.
这些全部指向了冰冷的事实
This all points to the cold hard truth
我们现任总统是一个外星人
that our current sitting president is an alien.
你做得很好
You do good work.
没什么好说的
What can I say?
我爱我的国家
I love my country.
我们没有叫你过来
We didn't ask for you to come here.
是你自作自受
You brought this on yourself.
你是谁
Who are you?
自由的代表
An agent of liberty.
卡兹尼亚南部边境